[
    {
      "question": "JavaScript is a _____-side programming language.",
      "answers": [
        "Client",
        "Server",
        "Both",
        "None"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Both",
      "canShuffle": false
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following will write \"Hello World\" in an alert box?",
      "answers": [
        "alertBox(“Hello World!”);",
        "alert(“Hello World!”);",
        "msgAlert(“Hello World!”);",
        "alert(Hello World!);"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "alert(“Hello World!”);",
      "canShuffle": true
    },
    {
      "question": "Which method would you use to find the minimum of x and y using JavaScript?",
      "answers": [
        "Math.min(x,y)",
        "min(x,y)",
        "min(xy)",
        "Math.min(xy)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Math.min(x,y)",
      "canShuffle": true
    },
    {
      "question": "Which \"if\" statement is correct to execute if \"x\" is equal to 2?",
      "answers": [
        "if(x 2)",
        " if(x = 2)",
        "if(x != 2 )",
        "if(x === 2)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "if(x === 2)",
      "canShuffle": true
    },
    {
      "question": "JavaScript has a file extension of:",
      "answers": [
        ".java",
        ".js",
        ".javascript",
        ".xml"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ".js",
      "canShuffle": true
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these is a valid variable name in JavaScript?",
      "answers": [
        "_data",
        "numbers&letters",
        "let",
        " 7days"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "_data",
      "canShuffle": true
    },
    {
      "question": "Which symbol is used separate JavaScript statements?",
      "answers": [
        ", ( Comma )",
        ": ( Colon )",
        "- ( Hyphen )",
        "; ( Semicolon )"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "; ( Semicolon )",
      "canShuffle": true
    },
    {
      "question": "Which JavaScript keyword is used to declare a variable?",
      "answers": [
        "Var",
        "var",
        "Let",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "var",
      "canShuffle": true
    },
    {
      "question": "How many keywords are there in JavaScript to declare variables or constants?",
      "answers": [
        "1",
        "2",
        "3",
        "4"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "3",
      "canShuffle": true
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the default value of an uninitialized variable?",
      "answers": [
        "0",
        "undefined",
        "null",
        "NaN"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "undefined",
      "canShuffle": true
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following represent falsy values in javascript?",
      "answers": [
        "false",
        "\"\"",
        "undefined",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "All of the above",
      "canShuffle": false
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following represent truthy values in javascript?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "{}",
        "[]",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "All of the above",
      "canShuffle": false
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of variable is declared by the following?\n<div class=\"snippet\"><span class=\"blue\">var </span>\n<span class=\"light-blue\">data</span>\n<span class=\"yellow\">[]</span>;\n</div>",
      "answers": [
        "array",
        "object",
        "data",
        "number"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "array",
      "canShuffle": true
    },
    {
      "question": "Which method is used to insert a new element at the end of an array?",
      "answers": [
        "unshift()",
        "push()",
        "pop()",
        "insert()"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "push()",
      "canShuffle": true
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following types of variable are only visible within a function where it is declared?",
      "answers": [
        "global variable",
        "local variable",
        "Both of the above",
        "None of the Above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "local variable",
      "canShuffle": false
    },
    {
      "question": "What will the output of the following code be?\n<div class=\"snippet\">\n<span class=\"light-blue\">console</span>.<span class=\"pale-yellow\">log</span><span class=\"yellow\">(</span>\n<span class=\"blue\">typeof</span>\n<span class=\"purple\">(</span>\n<span class=\"orange\">'1'</span>\n+\n<span class= pale-green>2</span>\n<span class=\"purple\">)</span>\n<span class=\"yellow\">)</span>;\n</div>",
      "answers": [
        "'boolean'",
        "'string'",
        "'number'",
        "'false'"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "'string'",
      "canShuffle": true
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following array methods removes the first element of the array and returns that element?",
      "answers": [
        "reverse()",
        "shift()",
        "slice()",
        "some()"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "shift()",
      "canShuffle": true
    },
    {
      "question": "What will the output of the following code be?\n<div class=\"snippet\">\n<span class=\"light-blue\">console</span>.<span class=\"pale-yellow\">log</span><span class=\"yellow\">(</span>\n<span class=\"blue\">typeof</span>\n<span class=\"purple\">(</span>\n<span class=\"pale-green\">6</span>\n/\n<span class=\"orange\">'3'</span>\n<span class=\"purple\">)</span>\n<span class=\"yellow\">)</span>;\n</div>",
      "answers": [
        "'string'",
        "'number'",
        "'integer'",
        "undefined"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "'number'",
      "canShuffle": true
    },
    {
      "question": "What will the output of the following code be?\n<div class=\"snippet\">\n<span class=\"blue\">let</span>\n<span class=\"light-blue\">stringVar</span>\n=\n<span class=\"orange\">'Hello World!'</span>;<br />\n<span class=\"light-blue\">console</span>.<span class=\"pale-yellow\">log</span><span class=\"yellow\">(</span>\n<span class=\"light-blue\">stringVar</span>.<span class=\"pale-yellow\">charAt</span><span class=\"purple\">(</span>\n<span class=\"pale-green\">5</span>\n<span class=\"purple\">)</span>\n<span class=\"yellow\">)</span>;\n</div>",
      "answers": [
        "l",
        "W",
        "o",
        "H"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "o",
      "canShuffle": true
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following represents loops in javascript?",
      "answers": [
        "for",
        "while",
        "forEach",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "All of the above",
      "canShuffle": false
    },
    {
      "question": "An object is an unordered collection of _______.",
      "answers": [
        "values",
        "names",
        "Properties",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Properties",
      "canShuffle": false
    },
    {
      "question": "Which method of an Array object calls a function for each element in the array?",
      "answers": [
        "forEach()",
        "every()",
        "forEvery()",
        "each()"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "forEach()",
      "canShuffle": true
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the correct way to write comments in JavaScript?",
      "answers": [
        "{# ... #}",
        "(! ... )",
        "// ....",
        "\\\\ ..."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "// ....",
      "canShuffle": true
    },
    {
      "question": "What company originally developed JavaScript?",
      "answers": [
        "IBM",
        "Microsoft",
        "Google",
        "Netscape"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Netscape",
      "canShuffle": true
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you call a function called myFunction() ?",
      "answers": [
        "myFunction();",
        "call myFunction();",
        "call function myFunction();",
        "myFunction;"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "myFunction();",
      "canShuffle": true
    }
  ]